[music]
Super duper love.
No, I ain't never been a feeling like
[music] this. Never had a feeling this
big. If I ever saw a sky full of
shooting stars and I'll be spinning
every [music] single wish on you. Now
I'm saying that I wouldn't do. I should
go make a monster shot. It's true. So
different [music] from the usual.
They're every kind of beautiful. My
heart's really going. Woah [music] woah
woah woah. Got to slow down. Got to cool
down from you. Woah woah woah woah.
[music]
I'm soing fireballing. I cannot lie.
[music] Because of you I'm flying high.
Because of you I'm looking up in the
sky.
Hand on [singing] my heart till death do
us part [music] the sweetest dino
boom boom [music] I'm about to explore
how can I feel more than this [music] I
don't know we got that super love
[music and singing]
super love
[music] my heart is too loud how can it
get better than it is [music] right now
we got Super duper love.
[music] Super duper love.
This love is so gigantic. [music] So
galactic, massive, so in no mess, just
like magic. I've been seeing stars and
caring all the stress like
desiraability. [music]
You and me beyond infinity got me up in
the air like
[music] taking me down kissing. We got a
problem cuz I lost control of emotional
hands on the wheel. Needing [music] more
oxygen, you are phenomenal. I could go
on and on about how I feel. Can't stop,
won't stop. I don't need a piss stop.
Fitting like a boom box. Now look what
you got. Hitting me like a bazooka.
[music]
Only one love super duper. Because of
you, I'm [singing] flying high.
Because [music] of you, I'm looking up
in the sky.
Hands on my heart [music] till death do
[singing] us part. The sweetest dyno.
[music]
How can it be a hard
la? [music]
[music]
How can we get better than it is right
now? We got [music] this super super
[singing] love super
la. [music]
[music]